One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all! Now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can! This moment...
We can! I can! With this feeling of freedom...
Now... Now, oh yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
Understood
It's Shanks!
Don't tell me you know him, Nekomamushi.
Yes, I know him!
"Red-Haired" Shanks, right?
I see!
No wonder that straw hat looks familiar!
Oh, does it?!
Inuarashi said that too!
Do you all know Shanks?!
Yes, because both the cat and I were once
traveling on Roger's ship.
What?!
Were you guys the Pirate King's crewmembers?!
Crewmembers...
Well, you can put it that way too but...
...we boarded many ships
as Oden-sama's attendants.
Even when we were traveling
on Whitebeard's Moby Dick.
And when Oden-sama was recruited by Roger,
we were always by his side...
Whoa, wait, wait! Whitebeard?!
Yes. We were still young...
...just like the apprentices
such as Shanks and Buggy.
Hey, wait! Stop! Stop!
I'm completely lost! Um...
But the two of us didn't
go to Raftel with them.
I said "Wait a minute"!
Um, first, on Whitebeard's ship,
there was Oden, the dog and the cat.
O
D
E
N
And then Oden was recruited by Roger
and you three switched to Roger's ship.
Yeah, I remember!
We were having so much fun at that time!
Oh, the species, geographical features, and climates
that I'd never seen!
The sea of clouds in the sky!
The island that floats undersea!
The sunlight!
Every day, I was very excited!
Those good old adventurous days!
You two were trying to kill each other earlier,
weren't you?
Then, Kin'emon, were you guys traveling
on Whitebeard's ship too?
No, we stayed in the Wano Country
the whole time.
Instead, we were trying
desperately to stop Oden-sama
from getting on board a pirate ship!
In the closed-off nation,
even leaving the country is a crime.
On the other hand, Oden-sama was a heretic
who had doubts about the law of the country.
We became acquainted with
Whitebeard, Roger and the
others when they landed on the Wano Country.
They were loyal to others
and we didn't think they were particularly bad people.
But I'd never heard of a daimyo
getting aboard a pirate ship so as his retainer...
So anyway, you all know Shanks!
And Rayleigh as well?!
Yes, of course!
If you got on board Roger's ship,
it must've been the Oro Jackson which was
built by my shipwright teacher Tom-san!
What?!
Are you the shipwright Tom's pupil?!
Um, can I go next?
Then, I bet you know Crocus the ship doctor...
Wait, Brook.
Sorry to interrupt you.
I gotta check something with them.
You said the four Road Poneglyphs will
show us the way to Raftel, right?
I'm starting to worry about the route.
Look.
The needles on the Log Pose!
Normally, we choose our next destination
looking at where these three needles point
but we're not tracking them now.
Is it okay?!
We met Tra-guy-kun
and came to Zou following the Vivre Card by chance,
and found the Road Poneglyph
which points the location of Raftel by by coincidence.
But according to Crocus-san
at the Twin Capes,
if you track logs,
every route will come to one in the end.
I'd always imagined that's Raftel.
Oh, Crocus!
I haven't seen him for a long time!
How is he doing?!
He was fine!
But that was two years ago!
You mean the old man who was with Laboon,
right?
Crocus the ship doctor! He-gara was looking for
some pirate group back in those days.
Oh, that was my group -
the whole crew is dead!
What?!
Hey! Listen!
I'm talking about something important!
Yes, I understand.
If you're interested where the logs will lead you,
go see for yourself.
There is definitely a route on which
all of those three needles point
in the same direction -
towards one specific place.
However, you-gara people have
already left on a journey
which lies beyond that point.
What? What do you mean?
You're supposed to find out about something
for the first time at the end of the route.
Find out the truth about
the Poneglyphs and the ancient script.
Find out about the civilization
that created those and the existence
of the hidden last island Raftel!
When Roger got there,
he had to do everything all over again.
Crocus was also part of the Pirate King's crew.
He is one of those who know everything.
He wouldn't tell a lie
unless he doesn't like you-gara guys.
I got it!
I didn't need to worry.
We weren't wandering off of the route.
I was just confused by the glimpses of the truth
we hadn't yet discovered.
The logs weren't lying!
Are you a navigator?
You're very dependable.
Don't worry! You're on the right track.
Just keep going!
Uh-huh!
Hey, hey! I don't know what
you guys are talking about
but don't you think our navigator's amazing?!
Am I dependable? Yes, I'm sure I am!
Yeah! The navigator of the next Pirate King!
How cool is that!
Don't hit me! That hurts!
Luffy...
It seems you-gara guys have been having fun
all this time.
Anyway, you guys are tied
to so many legends and
I feel dizzy like when I met Rayleigh.
I met Roger and the others too
but I don't remember clearly
because I was so young.
Oh, so you don't remember clearly...
I mean, no way! Roger died
more than two decades ago!
Who are you talking about?!
So much happened on Oden-sama's journey.
I'll tell you all about it sometime.
But for now, we have so many things to do
before fighting Kaidou!
We need to prepare.
Like I told you before, we're
trying to recruit samurai
who will fight with us
in the Wano Country now!
In the meantime, we've got
someone we need to see!
It's always good to have more reinforcements.
Who is it?
He is the former 1st division commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates...
Marco the Phoenix!
Marco?
--I didn't expect to hear that name here.
--Marco... Marco...
Oh! So you guys are friendly with him!
That's good to know!
If he can back us up,
that's going to be a tremendous help!
No but wait a minute.
In the event a year ago, they...
Well, don't expect too much.
Even if we can find him,
there's only a little hope.
Marco... Marco...
I'm sure I know him...
You must've met him
in the Paramount War at Marineford!
Marco... Who was it?
They say he ate a very
rare type of Devil Fruit!
What? Rare?
He looks like a pineapple.
Oh, that guy!
It was a major clash between the
remnants of the Whitebeard
Pirates led by Marco
and the Blackbeard Pirates!
It's been a year since
the so-called Grudge War,
but we haven't heard about what happened to
the commanders yet.
If he's alive,
I think I know where he would be.
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Did they fight against Blackbeard?!
They did.
Both sides had reinforcements.
It was quite a large-scale battle.
And Marco and the others
suffered a crushing defeat.
Blackbeard came to be recognized
as one of the Four Emperors after the war.
I didn't know that.
Damn, Blackbeard!
That was a major incident!
You really have no idea about
what happened.
Jinbe told me.
In the Paramount War,
after I passed out,
the Whitebeard Pirates saved my life.
The war is not over yet!
Take Ace's brother with you, Jinbe!
I wanna see him again and thank him.
So just like Kin'emon,
we need time to prepare too.
Okay, got it!
Then, let's split up for now!
We will round up allies
and plot a strategy in the Wano Country.
Are you gonna be okay there?
I thought you guys are being
targeted by the shogun.
But we're worried about our comrades there.
If you come on our submarine,
you'll be safe while traveling.
And...
...if you know a place to hide
on the island, you'll be alright.
I'll go look for Marco with my subordinates.
If Kin'emon and the others
are headed there first,
we'd better meet up in the Wano Country.
Let's make Kin'emon's Vivre Card.
Uh-huh, understood.
There he is! Raizo-dono!
Good to see you again!
What?
I'm glad that you're okay!
Raizo-san!
Y-You guys...?
Let's have a celebratory banquet.
It's ready!
A celebratory banquet?
What are we celebrating?!
Raizo-san's safety and...
The reconciliation of the two kings and...
The Kozuki Clan for reuniting safely!
Oh my!
You damn Minks!
Sorry for locking you up!
We wanted to save you-gara
from Jack and the others!
Raizo-san!
We tied up your hands - did we hurt you?
Ninpo!
I-love-you Technique!
Raizo-dono!
Nin! Nin! Nin! Nin!
All right! Let's have a banquet!
Banquet! Banquet! Banquet! Banquet! Banquet!
Banquet! Banquet!
Wait, Luffy!
We've already had a banquet!
Let's get going!
It's gonna be too late to save Sanji-kun!
What?! Are you coming?!
Of course, I'm coming with you!
I feel responsible.
Besides, do you think you can travel the sea
of the New World without a navigator?
I'm coming too! Pekoms is heavily injured!
Plus,
who is going to play music
when you guys feel down?
Who needs that?
Hey! Don't exclude me!
We both allowed them to take Sanji-san!
Kin'emon, do you mind if I take them with me?
You don't need my permission!
They're your crew!
And no one can stop someone
who is trying to save his friend!
I wish I could come along!
I'm in debt to Sanji-dono!
I'm sorry!
Now it's getting hard to sneak in.
Get out of there as soon as
you screw up the wedding!
We're gonna go along with Kin'emon
so you take care of Sanji!
Uh-huh!
Count on us!
Oh, Luffy.
In case you find a Poneglyph,
can you take a rubbing for me?
Okay!
So light-hearted!
I'll do research on the Poneglyph that Kaidou has
in the Wano Country too.
Great!
Alright! Is that all for now?
Hm? What's wrong?
What is it?!
Is that...
What?! What?!
The whole island is shaking!
Zunesha is crying out!
What's going on?!
Who's Zunesha?!
Huh? You're standing on it!
Oh! It's the elephant's name!
It's a big quake!
It's never happened before!
Who is it?! Whose voice is that?!
Run! It's gonna collapse!
Strong Right!
Get away from the building!
--Hold onto the tree!
--Okay!
This way!
Hurry up now!
Thank you!
Who is it?! Who's talking?!
My bone's gonna break, break, break!
My bones go crack, crack, crack, crack!
Momonosuke-sama! Are you hurt?!
What's happening to Zunesha?!
If you're there...
Wh-Who is it?!
--I hear the voice again!
--Momonosuke-sama!
Luffy, what's wrong?!
"What's wrong"?!
You hear it too, right?!
Huh?! Hear what?!
--No way!
--Can he-gara hear it too?!
Hurry up!
Who the hell are you?!
It's the loudest ever!
Fire!
It's starting to work!
No wonder.
Normal elephants are panicked
by just one bee.
Take a good look at its body.
If it's really been living for a millennium,
its skin must've gotten weak!
Is it a living legend?
No! It's just an old animal!
Concentrate fire on its left foreleg!
More volleys!
Keep shooting!
If we can make it bend its knees
and it brings its face closer,
we can finish it off as we like!
I'd like to gouge its eyes out
and cut out its tongue!
Maybe we can cut its stomach up from within!
Hurry!
Give me an order!
If you are there!
Give you an order to do what?!
Answer me! Who are you?!
We can't hear anything!
I can only hear his voice!
He's not listening to me!
What do you mean?!
What is going on?
Gol D. Roger...
And Oden-sama as well.
I heard they experienced the same thing.
They heard a loud voice, but they couldn't get it to respond.
Momonosuke-sama! Momonosuke-sama!
Momonosuke-sama!
What is this?
My head! My head... h-hurts!
This is...!
It's Jack!
Jack is...
Jack is attacking the elephant!
There are five powerful-looking ships at nine o'clock!
Zunesha is under attack?!
As I thought, Jack wasn't dead.
Momo! How do you know that?!
I don't know... I just saw it!
You saw?
It... It came to my mind...
I'm scared!
Send out the ships!
Return fire against Jack on the water!
Okay!
This is painful!
If I collapse,
it would put all of you in danger!
The one behind the voice is...
...this...
...elephant!
You mean Zunesha?!
Momonosuke-sama! What's going on?!
Again!
A long time ago, I...
A long time ago, the elephant committed a crime...
And now... all he is allowed... to do is... walk.
He has been... obeying that order.
Thus...
Shoot it up! Blow it away!
Thus, give me permission for once!
That worked! It's gonna collapse!
Order me!
To fight!
Momo!
You tell him! I have a feeling that your voice will reach him!
But...
If they bring down the elephant, we'll all end up in the sea!
But how loud should I be...
Just shout it out! Or the elephant will die!
A little more to go!
Don't give up, elephant! You can't fall down!
Make Jack...
Make Jack go away!!
Understood!
Trunk!
Jack-sama, our ship has been thrown into the air!
Oh...
Oh no-saru!
It quieted down.
What happened?!
I don't know. I don't see anything or hear the voice now.
Oh, really?! So Zunesha used his own trunk?
That's right-saru! With a single blow!
I can't believe it. I'd never thought Zunesha had a mind of his own.
Furthermore, we can even communicate with him.
Did Oden-sama know about Momonosuke-sama's ability?
Hey!
What's wrong? You guys still look serious.
We're stunned at this sudden occurrence.
First, we gotta find out how Jack was able to get here.
Otherwise, this place will no longer be safe.
I see. Well, good luck with that.
It'd be cool if this elephant becomes our ally.
That's easy for you to say.
Now, we're gonna go, so can we have lots of food?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
What do you want?
They say that communication with Jack has been suddenly lost!
Kaidou-san!
The medical knowledge of the now-named Sakura Kingdom
and the pharmaceutical knowledge of the Birdie Kingdom.
It's really incredible!
The bleeding has stopped.
You did great!
I prepared more than enough medicine,
so you'll be okay!
Only Dr. Chopper could've done it!
It's really amazing!
S-Such compliments...
...don't make me happy,
you fools!
Like you taught us,
we'll try to remove the bandages on a regular basis
to see how the wound is.
Good.
But even just changing the bandages is painstaking.
We'll be careful.
Yeah! Leave it to us!
Zunesha is our millennium-old land!
We might've gotten too comfortable and forgotten about it
because it's always been there since we were born.
Today, we were reminded.
We were reminded that we're always kept alive
by this great lifeform.
And it will come to an end one day.
If Zunesha, our land, has free will,
I want to ask him this now.
"You have been walking for a thousand years.
Where are you heading?"
Mokomo Dukedom, Kurau City
You want to stay? Here in Zou?
Uh-huh.
What are you going to do here?
I actually don't know what to do but...
Understood!
If it's possible,
I want to talk with him once again!
With Zunesha!
With the one who has been living for a millennium!
Why could he hear my voice?
Maybe he knows something about the Kozuki Clan!
--What?
--Momonosuke-sama!
I understand but there are people waiting for us
in the Wano Country...
That's all right, Kin'emon.
I've been thinking I still have to
protect this country from the threat of Kaidou.
We don't know yet how Jack could make it here twice
so we mustn't let down our guard.
We can't all get into the Wano Country
at once anyway.
I think I'll stay here for a while.
I'll bring Momonosuke-sama with me later.
Understood.
Nekomamushi made my Vivre Card earlier.
Give this to everyone.
Now, let's split up into four groups.
Search for Marco Wano Country Zou Whole Cake Island Team Nekomamushi Team Kin'emon Team Inuarashi Team Luffy
You can get there by following the Vivre Card,
but the problem is how we communicate.
In other countries, they use a snail to...
I mean, it's this big and if you speak into it,
someone at a distance will...
--Oh, you mean the Transponder Snail.
--Oh, that.
But in this country,
we're not accustomed to using them.
If you want a Transponder Snail,
I saw a wild one in the forest.
If you want one, I can set it up for you.
It's easy.
What??
Whale Forest
Hey!
The outskirts of the Guardians' dwelling
Pekomamushi's house is collapsed!
Hey, Pekomamushi!
Are you okay?! Answer me!
Pekomamushi! Where are you?!
I'm here! Grr!
Where are you?!
Look down!
A turtle?!
Step back!
How can I get a good rest?! Grr!
So you're Turtle-Mamushi!
Okay, so not only do you not remember my name,
but you also forgot that I'm a lion! Grr!
Of course, I could survive!
I ate the Turtle Fruit!
And my shell is as hard as a diamond!
Why aren't you listening?!
Chopper said he'll take responsibility
for treating you.
I see! You're not gonna
respond to the diamond part? Grr!
Ow, ow, ow!
But I appreciate his care.
I owe you guys a lot.
What?
What?!!
So let's go see Big Mom!
What?!
Wait, you bastard!
Don't you get it? I'm fatally injured now!
Hey! I'm injured! You've got to stop...
It's insane! I can't believe this!
You're the worst person to have debts to!
Guardians' Residential
District
Master.
Pedro.
Sanji saved this country.
And he was kidnapped in this country.
Even though the team has to be small,
we will fail in our duty...
...if no one from the Mink Tribe other than Pekoms
accompanies them.
You-gara, do you want to go along with Luffy?
I do!
Don't try to get the jump on the rest, Pedro!
That is a role that...
...we the Three Inuarashi Musketeers are
prepared to take on!
Back off, Shishilian!
A noisy guy like you is the least suitable for the job!
I'm not noisy!
Let me go!
I was with the Straw Hats the whole time!
Let me go too as an assistant to Dr. Chopper!
Wanda! Tristan!
We befriended Luffy after we fought him,
Pedro-san!
BB! Roddy!
Nami likes to sleep on my stomach!
That won't do them any good, Pastor Yomo!
I wanna chew on Baron Corpse's bones forever!
--Me too!
That's just your own goal! Shut up, dogs!
I understand how you all feel!
But you have to...
...let Pedro handle it!
Why, Master?!
Because Pekoms will be there.
Only Pedro can get him-gara under control!
Something is going on over there.
I called the last one "perfect" but...
...the new one surpasses that easily!
I incorporated
the growth capability of Pop Green
and got Franky's help
for the surface treatment.
It's not too much to say
that it's the greatest invention of the century...
You listening, Nami?!
If I squeeze here...
That was close!
It's a little too long, Usopp!
Listen to my instruction! You extended it too far!
You need some practice!
That's a new Climate Baton which you can extend
as you like with slight variations in handling!
I see!
I incorporated all the gadgets from Weatheria
that I got from you at Sabaody.
But just one thing...
You said to me at Sabaody...
It's like a magic wand!
I didn't understand what it meant.
It fits to my hand! It's easy to twirl!
--So it's up to you to decide.
--This is great, Usopp!
Wh-Wh-Wh...
What an advanced ninjutsu that is!
It's nice!
This sure is the culmination of
Weatheria's science of weather!
The Sorcerer's Climate Baton that I wanted!
Thanks, Usopp!
Don't mention it!
Now, about the cost...
Mirage Tempo!
Don't try to run!
The main gate of Zou
In the end, it's the six of us.
It's nice to have you, Peropero!
It's Pedro. I won't bother you.
Wh-Why's Big Bro Pedro coming, Grr?
I'll come along as someone who's known you-gara well
for a long time.
What do you mean by that?! Grr!
Nami! Take care!
Thanks! You too, Wanda!
Take care, Dr. Chopper.
Listen. We know him.
He could be dancing around like that
being happy about his marriage.
No way!
But I can't deny it!
Well, it's gonna be okay!
Alright, Luffy-dono!
We'll be waiting for you in the Wano Country!
Good luck, Luffy!
Take care!
Let us know if something happens.
I'll make a weapon to destroy Kaidou!
I'll round up the samurai in the Wano Country!
Now, I'll help you descend from the elephant.
That's okay, Kanjurou!
Bye!
Ya-hoo!
Leave Sanji in our hands!
What?!
See you in the Wano Country!
--Okay!
--Don't get caught by Big Mom!
She's the emperor of the sea!
Yeah! See you!
Thus, the Sanji retrieval team led by Luffy...
...sets out for the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom, who Luffy picked a fight with, waits.
Meanwhile, at the desert kingdom Alabasta
in the Grand Line...
Father-sama, hurry up!
Wait, Vivi.
Why are you in such a good mood?
Because it's been a while
since I went out to sea!